Sunshine现在有多个activity
finally sunshine has multiple activities and
我们可以使用intent在各个activity之间切换
we can move between then using intents
我们也学会了用隐式(implicit)intent去集成其他应用中的activity
we also know how to use implicit intends to integrate activities from other Apps
在这节课中，我们要学习Android系统是如何处理activity的
in this lesson will dive into just how the android framework deals with your
特别是activity的生命周期的概念
activities in particular how the activity light cycle may be different
跟你之前接触
from what you use to
的平台处理方式有所不同
from other platforms and environments don't worry there's plenty of code for
你需要写很多的代码才能体会到
you to write yes plenty of code blots lofts
下一步  我们要通过Sunshine中实现数据库存储
and lots of code will move sunshine along implementing
介绍使用content provider来抓取数据
underlying database and dropping that any content provider
以及如何使用一个持久的数据存储  我们的目标是  在网络非常慢或者
everything you need to know to use persistent storage the goal is to ensure
无法连接的时候  你的应用依然能够给使用者
your app provides a seamless efficient experience for your users
提供不间断的  响应快速的应用体验
even when networks may be slow or unavailable